MS. THI THI SHEIN



PERSONAL DETAILS

Mandalay, Myanmar thithishein.ucsm@gmail.com, +959967666620 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/thi-thi-shein-407655131

SUMMARY AND OBJECTIVE

As an assistant lecturer, experienced and passionate with over 3 years at the Computer University (Mandalay). Research assistant with over 5 years of experience in data mining research projects including spatial-temporal data analysis, pattern discovery, and behavioral tracking from moving objects' trajectories.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lecturer		Jan 2021 - May 2021

Faculty of Information Science, Computer University (Loikaw), Loikaw, Myanmar Subject: Database Management System (DBMS)

Research Assistant Aug 2017 - Nov 2020

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology, Ladkrabang, Bangkok, Thailand

Research Lab: Information Technology

Research Assistant Jul 2019 - Nov 2019

Tokai University, Tokyo, Japan Research Lab: Embedded System

Research Assistant Jun 2015 - Jul 2017

University of Computer Studies, Mandalay, Mandalay, Myanmar

Research Lab: Data Mining

Tutor Mar 2013 - May 2015

Faculty of Computing, Computer University (Mandalay), Mandalay, Myanmar

Subjects: Mathematics of Computing, Java

EDUCATION

D. Eng. in Electrical Engineering Aug 2017 - Jul 2020

King Mongut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang, Bangkok, Thailand

M.C.Sc. in Computer Science Dec 2009 - Jan 2012

Computer University (Mandalay), Mandalay, Myanmar

B.C.Sc. (Hons) in Computer Science Dec 2007 - Sep 2008

Computer University (Mandalay), Mandalay, Myanmar

2015

CERTIFICATES

Diploma in Java Programming Course May 2014

India-Myanmar Centre for Enhancement of IT Skills (IMCEITS)

Knowledge Co-Creation Program Nov 2019

(Computer and Information Engineering)

under the Japan International Cooperation Agency (JACA)

PROJECTS AND ACTIVITIES

Moving Objects Companions Discovery from Trajectory Data 2017 - 2020 Streams (Doctoral Thesis)

Robot IoT System Development and Platform (APRIS) Robot 2019 Challenge

IMCEITS Students' Alumni System (Project Competition at IMCEITS)

Electronic Products Forecasting System Using Greedy Genetic 2010 - 2012
Algorithm (Master Thesis)

SKILLS

Technical Skills

C++, Java, JavaScript, Python, SQL, ArcGIS

Soft Skills

Critical Thinking, Creative Thinking, Problem Solving, Active Learning

Hard Skills

Data Visualization, Data Analysis, Data Mining, Machine Learning, Programming

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Fully funded scholarship for D.Eng. from the AUN/SEED-Net Scholarship program (August, 2017)
- IMCEITS Students' Alumni System (May, 2014)

PUBLICATIONS

- 1. T. T. Shein, S. Puntheeranurak and M. Imamura, "Discovery of Evolving Companion from Trajectory Data Streams," Knowledge and Information System, Springer, vol. 62, no. 9, pp. 3509-3533, 2020.
- 2. T.T. Shein, S. Puntheeranurak, and M. Imamura, "Discovery of Loose Group Companion From Trajectory Data Streams," IEEE Access, vol. 8, pp. 85856–85868, 2020.
- 3. T.T. Shein, and M. Imamura, "Traffic Congestion Detection from Taxi Trajectory Data", Embedded System Symposium, pp. 94–95, 2019.
- 4. T.T. Shein, M. Imamura, and S. Puntheeranurak, "Significant Place Discovery from Taxi Trajectory Data",

- Asia Pacific Conference on Robot IoT System Development and Platform (APRIS), pp. 1–2, 2019.
- 5. T.T. Shein, A. Yamauchi, M. Imamura, and S. Puntheeranurak, "Discovering Group Movement Pattern by Measuring Individual Similarity from GPS Trajectories", Information Processing Society of Japan, Vol.2019-IS-150, pp. 1–2, 2019.
- 6. T. T. Shein and S. Puntheeranurak, "Incremental Clustering Approach for Evolving Trajectory Data Stream," 2018 International Electrical Engineering Congress (iEECON), Krabi, Thailand, pp. 454-457, 2018.
- 7. T. T. Shein, S. Puntheeranurak and M. Imamura, "Incremental Discovery of Crowd from Evolving Trajectory Data," 2018 International Conference on Engineering, Applied Sciences, and Technology (ICEAST), Phuket, Thailand, pp. 1-4, 2018.
- 8. T.T. Shein, S. Puntheeranurak, and M. Imamura, "Efficient Discovery of Traveling Companion from Evolving Trajectory Data Stream", Porc. IEEE 42nd Annual Computer Software Application Conference, pp. 448–453, 2018.